autodoc.co.uk 2016-05-13

# Privacy Policy

**Personal data**  
You can always visit our site www.autodoc.co.uk without having to enter you personal data. The only data saved is that provide you access, without specifying personal data (Internet Service Provider or the name of the files required). This data is used exclusively to improve our Internet offer and not to collect personal information.

We consider your personal data only when you send it to us voluntarily during the order process or when registering to get our information. The data you send to us is used without your consent only to fulfil your order. After concluding the contract and the payment, your data is blocked for further use and after the expiration of tax and trade procedures is removed, if you do not insist on further use. When you sign up to receive information, your email is used with your consent for personal advertising purposes, as long as you do not cancel your subscription.

**Transfer of personal data**  
Transfer of personal data is performed when delivering order, as far as it is necessary to deliver the goods. We transfer personal data required for the payment only to the banking institution.

**Cookies**  
We use cookies on various www.autodoc.co.uk pages to make visiting our web site more attractive and easier and make it possible to use certain features. Cookies are small text files that remain on your computer. Most of cookies we use are deleted from your hard drive after the browser session. They are called session cookies. Other cookies (long-term cookies) remain on your computer for a long time and allow us to identify you when you visit our site next time. Our partners are prohibited to use or process personal data. Most browsers accept cookies by default. You can change your security settings and accept or deny the temporary and saved cookies. In case you deactivate the cookies, come features on our site won’t be available. Some web pages may be displayed incorrectly. In order to use our shopping cart, temporary cookies must be enabled!

**Google Analytics**  
Our web page uses Google Analytics - Google company web analytics service. This service uses so-called “cookies”, text files that are saved on your computer. They let to analyse the use of the site. The information that is obtained from the cookies about your use of this site, as well as your IP-address, is transmitted to a Google server in the U.S. and is preserved there. Google uses this information to evaluate your use of the site in order to report site managers about site activity and to evaluate and provide services related to the use of the site and the Internet.

If it is required, Google may transfer this information to third parties unless it is prescribed by law or if the third party will process these data under instructions of Google. Google will not connect your IP-address with other data. You can prevent installation of cookies by changing settings of your browser software. In this case, you will not be able to use some features of our site in full if necessary. When using our site you agree the processing of data used by Google as described above and for the aforesaid purposes.Sites Autodoc GmbH contain links to third party websites. Autodoc GmbH is not responsible for the content of these sites. Their use is at your own risk.

**Data security**  
Your personal data will be coded and transfered via internet with SSL v3, SHA-1, With RSA Encryption, RSA with 1024 Bit not only by registration and in personal created profile, but also in entire field of shopping basket. We secure our site and other systems with technic and organizational actions against loss, destruction, access, change or proliferation of your data by unauthorized persons.

**Text of the agreement**  
We preserve the text of the contract and send you information about the order, as well as our General Terms and Conditions, by e-mail. You can look through these conditions any time here. Your order you can view at your account.

**Information, changing or deleting data**  
Under the Federal Data Protection Act at any time you have the right for information and the right to change or delete your saved data. If there are any legal, contractual, trade or tax terms or reasons not to delete your personal data, they will be blocked.

**Contact us:**  
Autodoc GmbH  
Josef-Orlopp-Straße 55   
10365 Berlin  
Germany

Director: Alexej Erdle

Tel.: +44 20 3322 2239  
E-Mail: [info@autodoc.co.uk](mailto:info@autodoc.co.uk)

Commercial Register: HRB 114045 B, local court Berlin-Charlottenburg  
IdNr.: DE260634589 

**Revocation of consent**  
You gave the following consent. We want to inform you that you can withdraw your consent at any time.
